{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Siding Painters","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/62495/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62495,"taskName":"Painting or Staining - Siding","taskDescription":"Paint or Stain Exterior Siding","xmTaskDescriptor":"Siding Painters","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"paint stain staining painting siding vinyl wood metal aluminum exterior","textMessagingName":"Siding Painting","rolloverLongDesc":"Siding painting including vinyl, wood, metal\r\nPainters generally also handle all relevant prep work including washing, scraping, sanding, caulking, patching \u0026 priming. Note separate categories for whole room painting, faux finishes, textured paint, murals, electrostatic painting, refinishing furniture \u0026 popcorn finishes.","rolloverShortDesc":"Siding painting including vinyl, wood, metal","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Paint or Stain Exterior House Siding.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated painters in your area.","htmlTitle":"Exterior Siding Painting \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Wood, Metal, Vinyl Siding Painting","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":55,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Paint or Stain Siding","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Exterior Painting or Staining - Siding","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Siding Painting Project","urlName":"Siding-Painting","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Metal, Wood, and Vinyl Siding Painters in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"paint stain staining painting siding vinyl wood metal aluminum exterior","emcCategoryOid":-12054,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9071,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62495/":{"taskOID":62495,"originalTaskOID":62495,"setID":9071,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5069,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1062,"questionDisplayText":"Existing home siding type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of siding is currently on the home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7089,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood siding","answerDisplayText":"Wood siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":773,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1112,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick siding","answerDisplayText":"Brick siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6165,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stucco siding","answerDisplayText":"Stucco siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5072,"questionDisplayText":"New color","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will the new color be:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5069,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1062,"questionDisplayText":"Existing home siding type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of siding is currently on the home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7089,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood siding","answerDisplayText":"Wood siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":773,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1112,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick siding","answerDisplayText":"Brick siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6165,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stucco siding","answerDisplayText":"Stucco siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7089,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood siding","answerDisplayText":"Wood siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":773,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum/Steel siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1112,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick siding","answerDisplayText":"Brick siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6165,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stucco siding","answerDisplayText":"Stucco siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5072,"questionDisplayText":"New color","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will the new color be:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}